They all have a great resume. They've
all been big- time quarterbacks. Um, and
whatever I can do to help the team win,
that's what I want to do.
>> Where did you improve when you went from
Minnesota to Ruckers? Where did you
really improve? Um, especially throwing
down the field last year.
>> Yeah, I think I improved in all areas of
my life. Um, number one, that was my
relationship with God. And then number
two, just being better with my
teammates, being with my teammates all
the time. Uh, just growing as a person
and as a player. I think, you know,
being young, uh, going into college and,
you know, having limited experience in
terms of reading defenses and doing
stuff like that, it took a lot of growth
for me to do and I'm just appreciative
for everyone that's been in my corner.
>> When were you here and when did you kind
of have those, you know, who did you all
talk to here and who kind of gave you a
good feeling?
>> Yeah, I mean, I was there about a week
and a half, two weeks ago now. Um, I
believe it was the 13th of April. Um, I
talked to everybody. I talked to all the
coaches. Uh, Coach Quinn, Coach Blau,
Coach Williams, um, Coach uh, everybody.
Literally everybody. I talked to
everybody. I shook hands with everybody.
And what I loved was how everybody is
connected. Everyone's together. And I
felt that when I went into that
building. The culture is live. Um, and I
come I come from a place with heavy
culture. So that's what I do. That's who
I live for. And I just I love being in
that building.
How do you feel about the offense that
David Blau wants to build here through
the some of the conversations you had
with the commanders?
>> Yeah, I'm really confident in coach. He
has a lot of experience. I was telling
him I remember watching you play in
college. Um so, um I can't wait. I can't
wait. I think he's a really smart mind.
I think uh I'm just really excited to be
there and that's really it. My emotions
are, you know, so high because I wanted
to be a commander and I'm just super
thankful for the opportunity they gave
me. What do you think about Jane
Daniels, Marcus Mariota?
>> Oh my gosh. I mean, two elite level
quarterbacks and you got Sam Hartman as
well who is an elite quarterback as
well. Um, I think those guys are I mean,
who else would you want to learn from?
Um, being in my position. I think being
able to, you know, be become the best
player that I could possibly can and
just get incrementally better every
single day, that's what I'm going to
show up and I'm going to do. What do you
what do you remember about facing off
against Sunny Styles and how excited are
you to be a new teammate of his?
>> Yeah, I mean Sunny, I told Sunny after
the Ohio State game, I said, "I'm gonna
see you again." And I was really
referring to the next level. Um, but
turns out we're on the same team. Uh,
he's a great football player. I remember
watching film on him and like, "This guy
can move. This guy can fly. This guy
could get to areas fast." Um, I was
really hoping I wouldn't have to play
against him. I'm happy he's on my team
for sure.
Is there any specific quarterback you
kind of modeled your game after as
you've grown in high school and college
or anyone you really idolized growing
up?
>> Yeah, like growing up I was a big 2000s
to like 80s 90s quarterback guys. So I
watch a lot of Rothllessberger
um you know uh Aaron Rodgers, Tom Brady,
Payton Manning, Drew Brees, Joe Montana.
I really love John Elway, Brett Favre.
you know, I grew up watching the guys
that um were pocket passers, but they
got out of the pocket and they can make
those plays. Um, and just yeah, I took I
I like to take something from everybody.
I like to take pieces from everybody's
game, even quarterbacks in college, guys
that were younger than me coming in and
I was taking pieces from their game. I
just like to take pieces from everybody.
I love to learn and I love to grow.
>> Why did you feel you're better throwing
the ball down the field last year? I
think it was just constant work with my
teammates, you know, throwing before
practice, throwing um, you know, off
season, every weekend, every day
throwing. Like we were always throwing.
We were building that connection. I
think that's what that's what made the
season what it was.
>> Going from Minnesota to Ruckers, I know
your OC made the same same transition.
What was what was it about that
relationship that made you decide that
was the best move for you?
>> Yeah, I know. Uh, I've known Coach
Saraka since I was 14 years old. And,
you know, once I went in the portal and,
you know, they offered me and told me
they wanted me to go there, I knew it
was a no-brainer just because of how
special that relationship is with Coach
Suraka. He's really special to me.
>> All good.
>> Congratulations.
>> Yeah. Thank you guys so much. I really
appreciate it.
>> Thank you. See you.
>> Thank you. All right. See you. All
right.